<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>devops with dunkin</title>
    <link>https://devopsdunkin.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on devops with dunkin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 21:10:42 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://devopsdunkin.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>terraform - dynamically created vSphere anti-affinity rules</title>
      <link>https://devopsdunkin.github.io/posts/tf-dynamic-vsphere-drs-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 21:10:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devopsdunkin.github.io/posts/tf-dynamic-vsphere-drs-rules/</guid>
      <description>As we&amp;rsquo;ve continued to mature our Terraform modules, we have been working to give our operations team more flexbility in how they are consumed. We wanted to make sure if more than one server was being deployed from a single configuration, that vSphere DRS anti-affinity rules would be created for them. I think we&amp;rsquo;ve all forgotten to create an anti-affinity rule or two. So now, our Terraform does this for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>terraform provider nagios</title>
      <link>https://devopsdunkin.github.io/posts/terraform-provider-nagios/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 07:20:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devopsdunkin.github.io/posts/terraform-provider-nagios/</guid>
      <description>For the past several months, I have spent several evenings learning how to write Go and how to create a Terraform provider. It&amp;rsquo;s been quite a fun experience and it&amp;rsquo;s exciting to see that work starting to pay off. As of October 31, version 1.0.0 has been released! This version allows you to manage hosts, host groups, services and service groups within Nagios XI. The plan is to release several updates over the coming weeks that will add other resources and eventually data sources into the fold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://devopsdunkin.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 07:33:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devopsdunkin.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name&amp;rsquo;s Chris and I am an infrastructure engineer with 10+ years working in IT in various industries. I recently started a new job back in February 2019 that got me involved with a lot of new tools. As I have been learning more about them and this whole DevOps methodology, I have stumbled across many things that aren&amp;rsquo;t well documented in the wild. So I started this blog to help fill that gap.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>